<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Map</title>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>Like other zoning overlays, HPOZs provide an additional layer of planning control during the project review process. All exterior work proposed in an HPOZ, including landscaping, alterations, additions, and new construction, is subject to additional review. Each district has a Preservation Plan with design guidelines and an HPOZ Board that reviews proposed work. Some projects are reviewed at a staff level, while others also go to the district’s HPOZ Board for consultation and review. Refresh Rate: Monthly</abstract>
            <purpose>The City’s local historic districts program aims to identify and protect the distinctive architectural and cultural resources of Los Angeles’s historic neighborhoods. Designating a neighborhood as a local historic district—also called a Historic Preservation Overlay Zone (HPOZ)—means that any new projects in that neighborhood must complement its historic character.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Historic Preservation</themekey>
                <themekey>HPOZ</themekey>
                <themekey>OHR</themekey>
                <themekey>Balboa Highlands</themekey>
                <themekey>Van Nuys</themekey>
                <themekey>Lincoln Heights</themekey>
                <themekey>Miracle Mile North</themekey>
                <themekey>Harvard Heights</themekey>
                <themekey>Gregory Ain Mar Vista Tract</themekey>
                <themekey>Western Heights</themekey>
                <themekey>Melrose Hill</themekey>
                <themekey>Carthay Circle</themekey>
                <themekey>University Park</themekey>
                <themekey>Banning Park</themekey>
                <themekey>La Fayette Square</themekey>
                <themekey>Vinegar Hill</themekey>
                <themekey>Adams - Normandie</themekey>
                <themekey>Spaulding Square</themekey>
                <themekey>West Adams Terrace</themekey>
                <themekey>Whitley Heights</themekey>
                <themekey>Stonehurst</themekey>
                <themekey>Windsor Square</themekey>
                <themekey>Hancock Park</themekey>
                <themekey>Angelino Heights</themekey>
                <themekey>Pico - Union</themekey>
                <themekey>Windsor Village</themekey>
                <themekey>Highland Park - Garvanza</themekey>
                <themekey>Jefferson Park</themekey>
                <themekey>Hollywood Grove</themekey>
                <themekey>Wilshire Park</themekey>
                <themekey>El Sereno-Berkshire Craftsman</themekey>
                <themekey>Sunset Square</themekey>
                <themekey>Carthay Square</themekey>
                <themekey>Miracle Mile</themekey>
                <themekey>Oxford Square</themekey>
                <themekey>Country Club Park</themekey>
                <themekey>27th &amp; 28th Street</themekey>
                <themekey>52nd Place Tifal Brothers Tract</themekey>
                <themekey>South Carthay</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE. BY USING THIS WEB SITE, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO BE OBLIGATED AND BECOME A PARTY TO THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS BELOW YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEB SITE. This web site is presented as a public service that provides Internet accessibility to information provided by the City of Los Angeles, Department of City Planning and to other City, State, and Federal information. Due to the dynamic nature of the information contained within this web site and the reliance on information from outside sources, the City of Los Angeles, Department of City Planning does not guarantee the accuracy or reliability of the information transmitted from this web site. This web site and all materials contained on it are distributed and transmitted on an as is and as available basis without any warranties of any kind, whether expressed or implied. The City of Los Angeles, Department of City Planning is not responsible for any special, indirect, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages that may arise from the use of, or the inability to use the web site and/or materials contained on the web site, or that result from mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion of files, errors, defects, delays in operation, or transmission, or any failure of performance, whether the material is provided by the City of Los Angeles or outside source. The City of Los Angeles, Department of City Planning reserves the right to modify, update, or alter these Terms and Conditions of use at any time. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your agreement to comply with such modifications. The information provided on this web site, and its links to other related web sites, are provided as a courtesy to our web site visitors only, and are in no manner an endorsement, recommendation, or approval of any person, any product, or any service contained on any other web site. The City of Los Angeles, Department of City Planning is neither responsible nor liable for any viruses or other contamination of your system nor for any delays, inaccuracies, errors, or omissions arising out of your use of this web site, or with respect to the material contained on the web site, including without limitation, any material posted on the web site. This Agreement shall be governed by, construed, and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of California as applied to agreements made and to be performed entirely therein. Any action brought to enforce the Agreement and/or in connection with this web site shall be brought in either the state or federal courts in the County of Los Angeles County, State of California.</useconst>
        <datacred>Los Angeles City Planning</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
